There is a massive push at the moment for
user-generated content where you use your
phone, you film it,
you edit it in Instagram edits,
and you post it.
Once you start getting busy as a personal
trainer, you set up your camera in the
corner,
you film yourself with your client,
you do voiceovers, you pick hooks, you
look for trends.
Get a little tripod like this,
you put your phone in it,
you start filming.
Then between clients,
you have a cancellation,
you go on the gym floor.
You may have seen one of these squat bars
before, and you're not quite sure what it
does or why your gym has one. This
is called the safety bar squat rack,
and in this
video I'm going to explain to you
everything you need to know.
You do a one-minute version for Instagram.
You do a seven-minute version,
you post it on YouTube.
You then do a written post,
you put it on LinkedIn.
And for the majority of you,
just trust me when I say this, and again,
this is a
video and I've got your best intentions in
heart, there will be a link in this
video for my PT starter kit
that teaches you all the things about
running a
business and making content
and all of that short.
Making 500 Instagram posts in the next
three months will do more than anything I
can sell you. Still buy my shit,
but honestly,
500 posts in the next three months.
Oh, it seems like a lot. Well,
someone else is going to fucking do those
posts if
you don't. In person,
100 people you approach, four
consults, three clients. And this
is me being kind of
optimistic. Online, and this
is going to depend on how good your
content is,
whatever, 1,000 followers,
200 people on your email list.
Out of that, 40 people seeing your offer,
let's say one person buys.